http://www.ivolatility.com/info/privacy.html

Futures Calculator
Future Volatility Ranker(IV)
Future Volatility Ranker(HV)
Futures Calculator
Future Volatility Ranker(IV)
Future Volatility Ranker(HV)
Futures Calculator
Future Volatility Ranker(IV)
Future Volatility Ranker(HV)
March 30, 2020
Dear IVolatility subscriber, we would like to give you an update on IVolatility's response to the COVID-19 outbreak.
We implemented measures to safeguard our team and fully transitioned our workforce to work from home status as of two weeks ago.
We can assure you that we will continue to operate our tools and services providing you and users around the world with crucial market volatility updates. Due to abnormal activity in the market, there is a strong technical overload on all data transmission channels, and we constantly monitor data services and adjust and split the data stream to process data without delays or interruptions. Further, our support and sales team are available as usual, and we are looking forward to hearing how we can help you!
We want you to feel informed and confident when working with us. We have several initiatives we're deploying to help our clients in this complicated time, including free subscriptions to our live market tracker, discounts on data, and more that will be announced very soon. We understand these are volatile times, but together we'll get through it stronger than before.
Take care of yourself and your family, safeguard your safety and wellbeing, and remember to wash your hands frequently.
We appreciate your loyalty, and we look forward to serving you with the most accurate, consistent, and up-to-date volatility data available, since for options, we are Big Data!
Thanks,
IVolatility team
Sales:
sales@ivolatility.com
Support: support@ivolatility.com
About Us
Security
Privacy Policy
Services Disclaimer
Awards
Partners
Knowledge Base
The following guidelines describe privacy policy of IVolatility.com website. By using this website, you accept all the terms and conditions in full.
Please read our Privacy Policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect and otherwise handle information about you. By using IVolatility.com services, you consent to the collection and usage of your data as described in this Privacy Policy. At IVolatility.com, we understand that the privacy and security of your personal and account information are important to you. IVolatility.com adheres to confidentiality standards that are designed to protect your personal information. We are committed to safeguarding your privacy online.
Information we collect
We collect information you provide to us when you create an account, update your profile, submit content, subscribe to our newsletter, participate in surveys, request customer support or otherwise communicate with us. The kinds of information we may gather include:
Basic user information, such as your name, username, email address, mailing address, phone number;
Other background information, contact and demographic information, such as your occupation, company information
Information We Collect Automatically
When you access or use IVolatility.com website and/or mobile app, we may automatically collect some information about you, including:
Location Information: We may collect information about your location when you access IVolatility.com website or mobile application.
Device Information: We may collect device-specific information when you access our Services, including your hardware model, operating system and version and information about the device's interaction with our Services.
Log Information: We may obtain log information about how you access or use our Services, including your access times, browser type and language, Internet Service Provider and Internet Protocol ("IP") address.
Information Collected by Cookies: We may automatically collect data using cookies and other tracking technologies in order to improve IVolatility.com services, user experience, monitor user activity, count visits, understand usage and campaign effectiveness.
Information We Collect from Other Sources
We may obtain information from other sources that use our services, such as your name, to provide, support, and improve the Services we offer.
Use and Disclosure of Personal Information
We may use and disclose Personal Information only for the following purposes:
To send you informational and promotional content in accordance with your preferences. You can stop receiving our informational and promotional emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in every email.
To provide information to representatives and advisors, including attorneys and accountants, to help us comply with legal, accounting, or security requirements.
To prosecute and defend a court, arbitration, or similar legal proceeding.
To respond to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.
To provide, support, and improve the Services we offer.
To transfer your information in the case of a sale, merger, consolidation, liquidation, reorganization, or acquisition of IVolatility.com.
Your Information Choices
We may only collect and process personal data about you where we have a lawful basis.
You have many choices about your data. You can add, update, edit your personal data through your account.
You can delete your personal data or your account on demand.
